这原是小事一筹
It used to be so simple
这世界我原已参透
It was a world I understood
在我不知的那迷雾背后
I didn't know what I didn't know
一切都乐悠悠
And life seemed pretty good
但现在黑恶涌起
But now the darkness rises
在我心 无底深渊里
From somewhere deep inside of me
那魔力握我于掌心
Her power all but takes me
能不能 封印这恶魔 在心底？
Can I keep this midnight from getting free?
如我能沐浴晴岚
If I can stay in the light
解放我自己
I know I'll be free
为完整自我守候
Then I can start to be whole
我会做回自己
I can start to be me
然而我 挣扎 无止息
But instead I am struggling
为我所见之谜
With all that I see
朋友们
And these friends
愿不见我黑暗的心
Mustn't see the midnight in me
那黑暗的心
The midnight in me-ee
愿不见我黑暗的
They mustn't see the midnight in
心
Meeeee